

MAGNUS BENNETT

DTU STUDENT

SKILLS

I learned programming six years ago and have made many coding projects since. I'm comfortable using Python, R, SQL and databases, since I have worked with all these during my education and made free time projects. I have also made many free time projects with C#, Unity and AI.

Because I am attending the Artificial Intelligence and Data programme, I have worked with machine learning, statistics, data analysis and visualization. In all the courses I have taken I have worked in groups, where several courses were focused on group projects. When I was on exchange in Korea I improved my English communication skills and learned programming related problem solving techniques, the C language and natural language processing (NLP).

EXPERIENCE

"LEKTIEHJÆLP" | MENTOR DANMARK | 26/05/2020 - 02/11/2021 At Mentor Danmark I learned to convey subjects like math in a simple-to-understand way.

ASSISTENT | FEST OG FARVER LYNGBY | 09/01-2020 - 01/03/2020 I learned to work hard, since Fest og Farver is very busy during holidays.

EDUCATION

C. ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AND DATA • 31/08/2020 - NOW • DTU Select courses:

- Introduction to programming and data processing (12)
- Introduction to machine learning and data mining (10)
- Introduction to mathematical statistics (10)
- Project in Statistical Evaluation for Artificial Intelligence and Data (10)
- Database Systems (12)
- Signals and data (12)
- Algorithms and Data Structures 1 (12)
- Advanced engineering mathematics 1 (10)

GPA (Danish scale): 10

MAT / IT • 01/08/2016 - 29/06/2019 • H.C. ØRSTED GYMNASIET LYNGBY

Select subjects:

- Matematik A (12)
- Informationsteknologi B (12)
- Programmering C (12)
- Engelsk B (12/10)

GPA (Danish scale): 9.7





